In the northwest of Italy,
There is a land surrounded by mountains.
Valle d'Aosta
Mont Blanc, Matterhorn,
Gran Paradiso,
Those giants of the Alps,
silently watching human's insignificance and courage.
Fifteen years ago, someone wanted to do a crazy thing.
to cross the giants' territory on foot.
So,
the Tor des Géants was born.
His name is Hai Guai.
He lives in Beijing and loves climbing mountains.
The tall one is Bai Rui.
He's from Northern Ireland.
They met on Strava.
He was also in Beijing at that time.
Later, almost every weekend,
They went into the mountains together.
Until Bai Rui returned to London.
They were busy with their own affairs
and it was hard to meet and climb together.
Until one day,
Hai Gui and Bai Rui made an appointment
to explore the long-awaited “Tor des Géants” together.
They will explore the Aosta Valley,
and cross three hundred and thirty kilometers together.
And this story belongs to them,
begins.
Yesterday, I ran over four thousand eight hundred.
Elevation gain？
Ah.
Forty-six kilometers.
Ah, forty-six kilometers.
Over four thousand eight hundred elevation gain.
Hai Gui said he wasn't preparing for the race,
It's just daily training.
But for others, this daily routine,
It would be written in their resumes.
Look at these two pairs of shoes.
How many kilometers can a pair of shoes run？
Running in the forest,
to him,
is returning to nature.
and back to himself.
Every weekend,
he goes into the mountains to charge his life.
The daily training of trail runners in Beijing,
is all around here.
which is very familiar to everyone.
When Bai Rui and I were running in Sanfeng,
We discussed whether,
we should sign up for a race together.
After he returned to London,
We agreed to explore some mountains together,
this opportunity may become less and less.
Races becomes a better form.
I would like to participate in a multi-day race.
We can spend a lot of time together.
If we really run a hundred kilometers,
or a hundred-mile race,
we wouldn't even have time to meet after the race.
But multi-day races might be much better.
My name is Tom, I'm from Ireland originally,
But I live in London now.
And London is a big city far away from mountains.
But every weekend I get out either to the local hills.
We did a few runs together and quite
Quickly realized that our attitudes towards
running and trail running is very similar.
Which is like using it as a way to explore the mountains,
explore wilderness.
And to discover new paths and new routes to travel
And so on. Yeah.
We quickly realized that
We had a kind of connection there, it was around there
He took the photo from a slightly different angle.
In twenty twenty one, end of January twenty twenty one.
Yeah, get through to fifty kilometers,
changed clothes there. I will follow you if i could.
I think I can't follow.
I think Tom are in good condition.
You're better than me.
Many people said that
When you reach fifty or one hundred kilometers,
you may feel the most tired and painful.
Then take a walk.
You rarely have the opportunity to
In a perfect state to compete.
I think, and
the essence of Ultra is that
You will definitely encounter problems.
Then you encounter problems,
And then
Encounter problems,
Solve problems.
Within three hundred kilometers,
You will definitely encounter many problems.
Have you look carefully at this,
What
It's only two kilometers away.
There is a "W".
It's a waypoint.
It's a way point, but there is no.
No supplies.
OK, um.
Uh, yes.
Aid A for aid aid may have some.
It should be Refreshment.
It's not, it's refreshment. Refreshment. Okay.
This is.
It's looks like The Lord of the Rings.
The Lord of the Rings.
6、5、4
3、2、1
Go.
Before starting the race,
I didn't really understand how long three thirty was.
I mean i know it was much longer than I'd run before.
But it's still hard to
comperhanding exactly what that feels like.
It's not like,
I wasn't running on the day and sleeping at night.
Like some days,
I sleep for an hour or two in the early morning,
or sleep bit  in the middle of the day, and then keep going.
In fact, you are like a student,
and you do a lot of exam questions.
When you face something like,
such as the Tor des Géants.
it may be a new exam,
It will take the knowledge points you have learned,
and then reassemble them.
When you face these again,
You may not have that,
the painful feeling you mentioned.
Sometimes you might even feel,
a little happy about hitting the question.
Where's Bai Rui(Tom)？
Bai Rui should be behind.
He's Bib is sixty-three, and I'm sixty-four.
I didn't expect
Are you cold？
It's okay, I've been keeping warm.
Is it okay？ Are you cold？
I am okay.
Water.
To the challenges over those days.
Another surprising thing is just how little sleep one needs.
I mean I got far more sleep than Hai Guai.
But it was still only like eight hours or something.
Kyle, you've worked hard.
Bai Rui has long Stride Length.
I could run while he could walk.
Really.
I mostly felt fine.
There was one time,
where I went over some kind of limit of,
not having enough sleep.
But after that I managed to deal with it fairly well.
And I realized that,
Actually like sometimes you only need an hour of sleep,
and then you can keep going.
Bai Rui and I were both exhausted.
And that mountain,
It felt like we were zigzagging up the mountain.
On zigzag uphill,
But it is.
It was very gentle, but then we got angry,
And started to climb straight up.
I felt like i was blew up.
Two three-kilometer mountains.
The first one was difficult.
The second one was even harder.
The only times I felt like I really wanted this to finish,
or like I really wanted to get to the next aid station,
or whatever was on some of the really long downhill.
There were some really long downhill sections,
That were just,
painful, and I mean that's why,
that's why,
My quads froze up at the end because of those downhills.
But other than that, I mean,
going up the mountains, I don't know.
I never felt like I wanted it to end,
or whatever I kind of,
I just wanted to keep going.
Keep climbing even on the last climb there.
I was saying I think we were both wrecked,
but Hai Guai actually looked pretty lively.
How about the evening?
At night,
Uh.
It was miserable.
Especially on the last mountain,
After climbing the last mountain,
we sat at the saddle in a daze,
We watched the sunrise,
and then we mustered up the courage to continue.
Uh, I
Actually, we can together run to here,
I already felt quite surprised.
Because he was in a very good state,
And I didn't seem to be in any mood.
Just mechanically,
put one foot in front of the other,
and keep going.
Don't think about what's behind.
Because there are more difficult things waiting for you.
Bravo.
Thank you.
I didn't feel like I was back on earth.
Because I will go back to the mountain later.
Only returning to Courmayeur is called returning to earth.
It felt so familiar,
Because it's what me and Hai guai have done before.
Although not for many many years,
I've seen Hai guai a few times over the last few years,
but for fairly short runs.
But yeah.
Three or four or five years ago,
we did long runs together and formed that connection.
Which I don't know what the word to describe it,
but there's some kind of connection of like,
Moving forward together, doing something together,
doing a big challenge and yeah,
It felt like we were right back in that.
After three or four years of,
not doing that.
Yeah, I mean we talked about stuff as well,
but it was a lot of time just yeah just moving together.
If you are so tired when arrive Donnas,
you can rest for long time there, I was thinking,
we should not so blow up.
In tune as well,
you kind of develop a kind of synchronization.
Where we both need to drink water,
at the same time or eat at the same time, and yeah.
This is just an interesting connection.
There will be long periods of silence.
I think this kind of tacit understanding is amazing.
Even when you don't talk,
you can also feel each other.
We are doing something.
You can feel what the other person seems to be saying.
Sometimes you may not want to say anything,
or suddenly think of something.
I've always been curious about it,
but it happens to be his strength.
At this time,
and discuss it.
Time to rest.
Yes, let's take a nap.
Finally, I can sleep.
Finally finally.
Oh my god.
I've been on the road for almost thirty hours.
Can we sleep now？
I'll go to sleep first.
I can't hold on anymore, I'm so sleepy.
I'll go to sleep.
Yeah, I guess like
I kind of lost track of time in a way,
because I didn't have a regular sleeping pattern.
But you can still feel the kind of rhythms of the day.
And I guess like the difference with normal life is,
It's the rhythms of the day as defined by nature.
The sun and the moon,
not the rhythms of the day defined by,
human schedules and so on.
So for me,
in some ways,
I preferred running at night
because it was really peaceful.
there were less people around,
and less almost like less to think about.
Because it wasn't sunny,
it wasn't hot,
like you could just,
you just need to keep warm.
but in some places you need to keep warm.
But that's easy,
you just put on more layers,
and then keep going.
So I quite like getting long sections done at night.
And it's just easy to focus at night.
And then you also know that if you're starting to feel tired,
or whatever, you know that in a few hours time,
the sun will start to coming up,
and it's just beautiful and all your energy comes back.
He'll recover at night.
I think he's going to pull me apart. Let's go.
Let's go.
Oh my god.
This track.
It's indescribable.
Hai Guai said it was indescribable.
I think he was too tired,
so tired that even the wind became a burden.
But when they saw the mountains,
and clouds,
their eyes suddenly lit up again.
It's like outdoor people know that feeling,
body in hell,
and eyes in heaven.
And time,
is always contradictory.
They hope it goes faster,
so that they can end it all quickly,
but also hope it slows down,
because they don't want to fast-forward the scenery.
You really know how to choose the place.
The most beautiful internet-famous cottage.
The front and back of each saddle,
and temperature.
which are all different.
So when you come out of the forest,
you see the meadow or the stone sea,
your spirits will be lifted,
and the fatigue will be slightly relieved.
Every time around the top of the mountain is the essence.
I don't know it's really hard to comperhand,
before having done a race like this.
it's basically just one big climb,
because I slept in the Donnas.
and then leave until about half past,
eleven or midnight.
There's basically a two thousand four hundred meter climb.
But the things that surprised me I guess was,
where you go through ups and downs,
but in some ways,
you kind of feel stronger through the run.
Sounds weird to say that because obviously,
I slowed down and by the end like,
I was kind of injured on my quads, not really injured,
but it was overused and swollen.
But still at the end, when I was going uphill, at least,
I felt strong,
I felt stronger going up the final hill,
than the first few hills.
I felt like I had adapted.
the other thing I was thinking about quite a lot, at least,
while my brain was fairly awake,
and not too tired.
I was thinking a lot about how I wanted to,
come back to this area,
and explore other paths.
just like on my own,
not in a race format.
We crossed over so many different paths,
and there are so many beautiful places,
I'd like to go back to new places,
I'd like to explore.
Ten years ago,
when I saw others complete the Tor des Géants,
I was also a fat guy weighing one hundred seventy catties.
I also lost weight and then got into this sport.
If you really like it,
and think this film is good,
or the scenery shown in the film,
which touches you,
I think you can try to do it first.
The road is made step by step.
The important thing is to take action,
rather than choosing what to do.
Whether you choose Tor des Géants
or take a park hike,
or even just leave home and walk to a strange street,
these are both good things to you,
as long as you go out and experience,
and experience different things,
and accumulate them gradually.
I think you may have your own path.
It's not about completing the Tor des Géants,
or complete the PTL,
as your ultimate goal.
Don't take others' goals as your own.
Even if you achieve it,
you may not feel very happy.
You may even feel,
you may not know what to do next.
In the process of your own exploration,
have your own style.
Don't think that nature is,
may be defined as mountains, seas, lakes, and so on.
In fact, nature is the city where you live,
or maybe the streets where you live.
These are all nature.
Don't say that you only look at the world,
only through social media,
and see nature.
I think the best way is to go out and experience it,
and experience more.
Yes.
Oh.
When I was running in early times,
run one hundred kilometers,
or navigate myself to Wugong Mountain,
when I was in the forest and encountered spider webs,
my physical strength decreased,
and my face was covered with bugs,
I was very frustrated when I was covered in spider webs.
This is the mentality,
and gradually it may transfer to,
my current Tor des Géants.
when facing darkness, fatigue or injury,
I have to adjust myself.
how to cheer up and move on to the next supply station.
It should be the process.
I can only say,
the memories left by this place are so beautiful.
This place is really beautiful.
I will try to come back every year.
I will still train myself,
to make my next experence better.
Not that I'll get better results.
In the same time,
I might become more calm.
I think this is the goal I pursue.
When I get off work every day,
I run to the back mountain near my workplace,
and watch the sunset from a distance.
I can see the Qingshuijian Mountain,
I don't think,
the Alps are particularly important.
I feel like this.
Life is a,
circle.
Some people may draw a big circle,
and take many paths.
I may draw a slightly smaller circle.
I think it's enough.
The joy of doing this,
is not about the race.
It's about the feeling and connections we get,
with the mountains and nature,
and so on. Yeah,
so I'd like to come back and experience that again,
and just on my own,
or just with friends, design our own routes.
I can't think like exactly,
were there any major things I was thinking through,
while I was going up.
There's a few like I can recall a few things now,
that are not very interesting,
but I'm gonna say them anyway.
I noticed during particularly,
during the day,
just how many people were out and about in the mountains.
like old people,
young people, children, families,
hiking, running, and all that.
I just thought wow,
the outdoors culture here is so rich, it's really impressive.
So the title of this film,
Ephemeral mountains，
what does that like mean to you？
ephemeral？
It's like ephemeral mountains.
I don't got that，
I don't feel very ephemeral at the moment，
because they're hitting me in the face every day.
It feels very very real，
and very hard.
Obviously, if you train really hard，
like, I mean, like Hai Guai.
As I said before like, for Hai Guai,
I don't think it's like training per se.
it's not like he has a calendar of like a training plan.
just what he does.
but you know
He does a lot of mountains,
and with that you will be faster.
But I think the core skill in this,
really is understanding your body.
Like if you can understand how much water, salt, and food,
your body needs,
and if you can digest it properly and so on,
you can just keep going and sleep as well,
which is the bit I'm struggling with.
I never felt like I wanted it to end or whatever.
I just wanted to keep going,
keep climbing even on the last climb there.
I felt a lot of energy.
I would have been happy,
if that climb had gone on for another thousand meters.
You're still smiling.
I don't know, it feels good, and the views from every point.
It's not just the view from the top,
it's the view from every hundred meters.
Every couple hundred meters is different.
I've been waiting for it for
three hundred and thirty kilometers, and honestly,
when I got to the last pass,
you konw I was sad that it was the last pass.
I didn't want it to be the last one.
Weird to think that it's the last climb.
And it feels really special.
And I guess when I get back to normal life,
I'm gonna feel like I miss that feeling of,
pushing my body，
and feeling the connection with nature.
OK, thank you.
If you want something too hot, soup, tea, coffee.
OK.
where do you want？
Perfect, thank you, bye.
thank you too.
It's ephemeral.
I really feel like ephemeral.
It feels like a long time when you're in it.
Even after the first night,
I felt like I couldn't even imagine，
there are still three days left.
When you briefly let go of these thoughts,
you can't feel it.
As you walk, you don't realize that it's all over.
After climbing so many mountains,
Do you still like climbing mountains？
Of course.
I'm already looking forward to the next time.
Climbing so many mountains.
I feel like I didn't get tired to the top.
Today is so long.
I feel like I've been climbing for a long time.
Your pain is all told by your brain,
It's a lie, and it want you to fly a drone in the car.
It might be here now.
I just accomplished one thing.
that's all.
But as for,
in the future,
what impact it will have on your future life,
I said maybe.
I may only know when it happens.
As for now,
I don't think so much.
I don't think it's that important to finish this,
or how amazing it is.
It's over.
A man with thunder in his chest but calm face,
can be made a general.
I'm like with thunder now.
because my soles,
and it hurts a lot to walk on this road.
Hai Gui and Bai Rui,
have finally completed their giant journey.
For us,
Alps is too far,
three hundred and thirty kilometers is too hard.
But when you open the door and go out,
your nature is right beside you.
When you really come back, this is the scene.
Maybe on the way,
you've thought about it countless times.
I've thought about it countless times.
The breakfast we had in the morning,
It was the happiest time.
Maybe the happiest time of the year.
It's happier than the Spring Festival.
How did you get up here？
Can you drive to the halfway up？
No, I can't.
Oh my.
We climb here.
You are the man Director Jia.
Call Xiaoqin.
Here comes.
You are the best.