In northwestern Italy,
there is a land surrounded by mountains.
Valle d'Aosta.
Mont Blanc, Matterhorn,
Gran Paradiso,
Those giants of the Alps,
silently witnessing human insignificance and courage.
Fifteen years ago, someone decided to do something crazy.
to cross the giants' territory on foot.
So,
the Tor des Géants was born.
His name is Hai Guai.
He lives in Beijing and loves climbing mountains.
The taller one is Bai Rui.
He's from Northern Ireland.
They met on Strava.
He was also living in Beijing at the time.
After that, almost every weekend,
they went into the mountains together.
Until Bai Rui returned to London.
they each got busy with their own lives,
and it became hard to meet up and climb together.
Until one day,
Hai Guai and Bai Rui decided
to take on the long-awaited Tor des Géants together.
They would cross the Aosta Valley,
covering 330 kilometers together.
And this is where
their story begins.
Yesterday, I did over 4,800 meters.
Of elevation gain?
Ah.
In forty-six kilometers.
Ah, forty-six kilometers.
Over 4,800 meters of elevation gain.
Hai Gui said he wasn't preparing for the race,
It was just a regular training day.
But for most people, a daily routine like that,
would be resume-worthy.
Look at these two pairs of shoes.
How many kilometers can one pair of shoes run?
For him, running in the forest,
to him,
is a way of returning to nature
and to himself.
Every weekend,
he heads into the mountains to recharge.
This is where trail runners in Beijing
do their everyday training.
Everyone knows this place well.
When Bai Rui and I were running in Sanfeng,
we talked about whether
we should sign up for a race together.
After he moved back to London,
we knew that chances to explore the mountains together,
would only get rarer.
A race felt like the best way to do it.
I wanted to do a multi-day race.
That way, we could spend a lot of time together.
If we just ran a 100K,
or a hundred-miler,
we probably wouldn't even have time to hang out afterward.
A multi-day race seemed much better.
My name is Tom. I'm originally from Ireland,
but I live in London now.
And London is a big city, far from the mountains.
But every weekend, I get out to the local hills.
We did a few runs together and
quickly realized that our attitudes toward
running and trail running were very similar,
that we both used it as a way to explore the mountains,
to explore the wilderness,
and to discover new paths and new routes.
That sort of thing. Yeah.
We quickly realized
that there was a real connection there.
He just took the photo from a slightly different angle.
At the end of January 2021.
Yeah, get to 50 kilometers,
change clothes there. I'll follow if I can.
I don't think I can keep up.
I think Tom is in good shape.
You're better than I am.
A lot of people say that
when you hit 50 or 100 kilometers,
that's when you feel the most tired and the most pain.
Then just walk for a while.
You rarely get the chance
to race in perfect condition.
I think
the essence of ultra running is that
you're definitely going to run into problems.
Then you deal with one problem,
And then
another problem,
and solve it.
Over 300 kilometers,
you're definitely going to face plenty of problems.
Have you looked closely at this?
What?
It's only two kilometers away.
There's a "W".
It's a waypoint.
It's a waypoint, but there's
no aid there.
Okay, um...
Uh, yes.
Aid stations may have some.
It should say refreshment.
No, not aid, refreshment. Refreshment. Okay.
This place...
It looks like The Lord of the Rings.
The Lord of the Rings.
6, 5, 4
3, 2, 1
Go.
Before starting the race,
I didn't really understand what 330 kilometers meant.
I knew it was much longer than anything I'd run before,
but it was still hard to
fully comprehend what that would feel like.
It wasn't like
I'd run during the day and sleep at night.
Some days,
I'd sleep for an hour or two in the early morning,
or a bit in the middle of the day, and then keep going.
In a way, it's like being a student
who has done a lot of practice questions.
When you face something
like the Tor des Géants,
it may be a new exam,
but it just takes everything you've learned
and rearranges it.
When you face those things again,
you may not even have
the pain you were talking about.
Sometimes you might even feel
a little happy to see the question.
Where's Bai Rui... Tom?
Bai Rui should be behind us.
His bib is 63, and mine is 64.
I didn't expect that.
Are you cold?
It's okay. I've been keeping warm.
Are you okay? Are you cold?
I'm okay.
Water.
To the challenges ahead.
Another surprising thing is how little sleep you actually need.
I mean, I got far more sleep than Hai Guai.
But it was still only about eight hours in total.
Kyle, you've worked hard.
Bai Rui has a long stride.
I have to run while he's just walking.
Really.
I mostly felt fine.
There was one point
when I hit some kind of limit
from not getting enough sleep.
But after that, I managed it pretty well.
And I realized
that sometimes an hour of sleep is enough,
and then you can keep going.
Bai Rui and I were both exhausted.
And on that mountain,
it felt like we were just zigzagging forever.
The switchbacks
were gentle,
but then we got frustrated
and started climbing straight up.
I felt completely blown up.
Two three-kilometer climbs.
The first one was hard.
The second one was even harder.
The only times I really wanted it to end
or really wanted to reach the next aid station
were on some of the really long downhills.
There were some downhill sections
that were just
painful, and I mean,
that's why,
my quads seized up at the end.
But other than that,
going up the mountains,
I never really felt like I wanted it to end.
If anything,
I just wanted to keep going.
Keep climbing, even on the last ascent.
I think we were both wrecked,
but Hai Guai still looked pretty lively.
What about at night?
At night,
uh...
it was miserable.
Especially on the last mountain.
After we climbed it,
we sat at the saddle in a daze.
We watched the sunrise,
and then forced ourselves to keep going.
Uh, I...
Honestly, the fact that
we made it this far together
already surprised me.
Because he was still in great shape,
and my mind was basically blank.
I was just
putting one foot in front of the other.
Don't think about what's behind you.
Harder things are still waiting ahead.
Bravo.
Thank you.
I didn't feel like I was back on earth.
Because I was heading back into the mountains later.
Only getting back to Courmayeur feels like returning to earth.
It felt so familiar,
because it's what Hai Guai and I used to do.
Not for many years, of course,
I've seen Hai Guai a few times over the last few years,
but only for fairly short runs.
But yeah,
three, four, five years ago,
we did long runs together and built that connection.
I don't quite know how to describe it,
but it's some kind of bond,
moving forward together,
taking on something big together.
It felt like we were right back there.
Even after three or four years
of not doing that.
Yeah, I mean, we talked as well,
but a lot of the time we were just moving together.
If you're really tired when you get to Donnas,
you can rest there for a long time.
I was thinking we shouldn't blow ourselves up.
And in that rhythm,
you develop a kind of synchronization.
We'd want to drink water
or eat at the same time.
It's a fascinating connection.
There can be long stretches of silence.
That kind of unspoken understanding is amazing.
Even when you don't talk,
you can still feel each other.
Like you're doing the same thing together.
You can almost sense what the other person is thinking.
Sometimes you don't want to say anything,
or something suddenly occurs to you.
I've always been curious about that,
and it just happens to be one of his strengths.
At moments like that,
we talk it through.
Time to rest.
Yeah, let's take a nap.
Finally, I can sleep.
Finally.
Oh my God.
I've been out on the course for almost thirty hours.
Can we sleep now?
I'll sleep first.
I can't hold on anymore. I'm so sleepy.
I'm going to sleep.
Yeah, I guess
I kind of lost track of time,
because I didn't have a regular sleep pattern.
But you could still feel the rhythms of the day.
And I guess the difference from normal life is
that those rhythms are defined by nature,
by the sun and the moon,
not by the rhythms
of human schedules and routines.
So for me,
in some ways,
I preferred running at night,
because it was really peaceful.
There were fewer people around,
and almost less to think about.
Because it wasn't sunny
and it wasn't hot.
You could just,
you just had to keep warm.
In some places, anyway.
But that's easy.
You just put on more layers
and keep going.
So I quite liked getting long sections done at night.
And it's just easier to focus at night.
And you also know that if you're starting to feel tired,
or whatever, you know that in a few hours,
the sun will start coming up,
and it's so beautiful that all your energy comes back.
He comes alive at night.
I think he's going to tear me apart. Let's go.
Let's go.
Oh my god.
This trail...
It's indescribable.
Hai Guai said it was indescribable.
I think he was just too tired,
so tired that even the wind felt like a burden.
But when they saw the mountains
and the clouds,
their eyes lit up again.
People who spend time outdoors know that feeling:
your body is in hell,
but your eyes are in heaven.
And time
is always contradictory.
They want it to go faster
so they can get it over with,
but they also want it to slow down,
because they don't want to fast-forward through the scenery.
You really know how to pick a spot.
The prettiest internet-famous hut.
On either side of every saddle,
the temperature
can be completely different.
So when you come out of the forest
and see the meadow or the boulder field,
your spirits lift,
and the fatigue eases a little.
Every stretch around a summit is the essence of it.
I don't know. It's really hard to comprehend
before you've done a race like this.
It's basically one huge climb,
because I slept in Donnas
and then left at around
eleven-thirty or midnight.
There's basically a 2,400-meter climb.
But one thing that surprised me was
that even with all the ups and downs,
in some ways
you actually feel stronger as the race goes on.
It sounds strange to say that because obviously
I slowed down, and by the end
my quads were kind of injured, not really injured,
but overused and swollen.
But even so, on the final climb,
I felt strong,
I felt stronger on the last hill
than I did on the first few.
I felt like I'd adapted.
The other thing I was thinking about a lot,
whenever my brain was still awake
and I wasn't too tired,
was how much I wanted to
come back to this area,
and explore other paths,
just on my own,
outside of a race format.
We crossed so many different trails,
and there are so many beautiful places,
I'd like to come back to new places,
to keep exploring.
Ten years ago,
when I saw others complete the Tor des Géants,
I was still a chubby guy weighing about 85 kilos.
I lost weight, and then I got into the sport.
If you really like it,
and if this film moves you,
or if the scenery in the film
speaks to you,
I think the first thing is just to try.
The path is made one step at a time.
What matters is taking action,
not obsessing over what to choose.
Whether you choose the Tor des Geants
or just go for a hike in a park,
or even leave home and walk down an unfamiliar street,
all of those things are good for you,
as long as you go out and experience them,
keep experiencing different things,
and let them accumulate over time.
I think you'll find your own path.
It's not about finishing the Tor des Geants,
or completing the PTL,
as some ultimate goal.
Don't make other people's goals your own.
Even if you achieve them,
you may not feel that happy.
You may even find
you don't know what to do next.
In the course of your own exploration,
you should have a style of your own.
Don't think that nature
has to mean mountains, seas, lakes, and so on.
In fact, nature can be the city you live in,
or the streets you walk every day.
All of that is nature too.
Don't just
only through social media,
and nature through social media.
I think the best way is to go out and experience it,
and experience more of it.
Yes.
Oh.
Back when I first started running,
whether it was a 100-kilometer race
or navigating my own way through Wugong Mountain,
when I was in the forest and hit spider webs,
my energy dropped,
and my face was covered with bugs,
Getting tangled in spider webs was so frustrating.
But that mindset
gradually carried over into
my Tor des Geants today.
When I face darkness, fatigue, or injury,
I have to keep adjusting myself,
find a way to lift my spirits and get to the next aid station.
It should be the process.
All I can say is
the memories this place left me are so beautiful.
This place is truly beautiful.
I'll try to come back every year.
I'll keep training
so that next time the experience can be even better,
not so that I can get a better result.
At the same time,
I may become calmer.
I think that's the goal I'm pursuing.
After work every day,
I run up the hill behind my workplace
and watch the sunset from afar.
I can see Qingshuijian Mountain.
I don't think,
the Alps are all that important.
That's how I feel.
Life is a,
circle.
Some people may draw a big circle
and take many paths.
I might draw a slightly smaller loop.
I think that's enough.
The joy of this,
isn't really about the race.
It's about the feeling and the connection we have,
with the mountains and with nature.
That's really it. Yeah.
So I'd love to come back and feel that again,
either on my own,
or with friends, designing our own routes.
I can't say exactly,
whether there were any big things I was thinking through
while I was climbing.
There are a few things I can remember now,
nothing especially interesting,
but I'll say them anyway.
One thing I noticed,
especially during the day,
was just how many people were out in the mountains.
Older people,
young people, children, families,
hiking, running, all of it.
I just thought, wow,
the outdoor culture here is so rich. It's really impressive.
So the title of this film,
Ephemeral Mountains,
what does that mean to you?
Ephemeral?
As in "Ephemeral Mountains"?
I don't really buy that.
I don't feel anything ephemeral right now,
because they're hitting me in the face every day.
It feels very, very real,
and very hard.
Obviously, if you train really hard,
like Hai Guai does.
But as I said before, for Hai Guai,
I don't even think of it as training, exactly.
It's not like he follows some training calendar.
That's just what he does.
But, you know,
he spends a lot of time in the mountains,
and that naturally makes you faster.
But I think the core skill here,
is really understanding your body.
If you know how much water, salt, and food
your body needs,
and you can actually digest it properly,
then you can just keep going. Sleep matters too,
and that's the part I struggle with.
I never really wanted it to end.
I just wanted to keep going,
keep climbing, even on that last climb.
I felt full of energy.
Honestly, I would've been happy
if that climb had gone on for another thousand meters.
You're still smiling.
I don't know, it just feels good. And the views are amazing.
It's not just the view from the top,
it's the view every hundred meters.
Every few hundred meters, it's different.
I'd been waiting for it for
all 330 kilometers, and honestly,
when I reached the last pass,
I was sad it was the last one.
I didn't want it to be the last.
It's strange to think that was the final climb.
And it feels really special.
And I guess when I get back to normal life,
I'm going to miss that feeling of
pushing my body,
and feeling that connection with nature.
Okay, thank you.
If you want something hot, soup, tea, coffee...
Okay.
What would you like?
Perfect, thank you. Bye.
Thank you too.
It's ephemeral.
I can really feel that now.
It feels like a long time while you're inside it.
Even after the first night,
I felt like I couldn't even imagine
there were still three days left.
But the moment you stop thinking about it,
you can hardly feel it at all.
You just keep moving, and suddenly it's over.
After climbing so many mountains,
do you still like climbing?
Of course.
I'm already looking forward to the next one.
After climbing that many mountains,
I still don't feel tired of climbing.
Today was so long.
I feel like I've been climbing forever.
All that pain is just your brain talking.
It's lying to you. It wants you back in the car.
Maybe that moment is right now.
I feel like I've only done one thing.
That's all.
But as for
what it might mean,
for my life in the future,
maybe
I'll only know when it happens.
But for now,
I don't think about it much.
I don't think finishing this matters that much,
or that it's something incredible.
It's over now.
A man with thunder in his chest and a calm face
is fit to be a general.
Right now, I'm all thunder inside,
because the soles of my feet...
it hurts like hell to walk on this road.
Hai Guai and Bai Rui
have finally completed their journey of giants.
For us,
the Alps are too far away,
and 330 kilometers feels impossible.
But the moment you step outside,
nature is already right beside you.
When you really come back, this is what it looks like.
Maybe out there,
you imagined it countless times.
I've imagined it countless times.
That breakfast we had this morning,
was the happiest moment.
Maybe the happiest of the year.
Happier than Spring Festival.
How did you get up here?
Can you drive halfway up?
No, you can't.
Oh my.
We climbed all the way up here.
You're the man, Director Jia.
Call Xiaoqin.
Here she comes.
You're the best.