Are you okay? Are you cold?
I'm okay.
Water.
To the challenges ahead.
Another surprising thing is how little sleep you actually need.
I mean, I got far more sleep than Hai Guai.
But it was still only about eight hours in total.
Kyle, you've worked hard.
Bai Rui has a long stride.
I have to run while he's just walking.
Really.
I mostly felt fine.
There was one point
when I hit some kind of limit
from not getting enough sleep.
But after that, I managed it pretty well.
And I realized
that sometimes an hour of sleep is enough,
and then you can keep going.
Bai Rui and I were both exhausted.
And on that mountain,
it felt like we were just zigzagging forever.
The switchbacks
were gentle,
but then we got frustrated
and started climbing straight up.
I felt completely blown up.
Two three-kilometer climbs.
The first one was hard.
The second one was even harder.
The only times I really wanted it to end
or really wanted to reach the next aid station
were on some of the really long downhills.
There were some downhill sections
that were just
painful, and I mean,
that's why,
my quads seized up at the end.
But other than that,
going up the mountains,
I never really felt like I wanted it to end.
If anything,
I just wanted to keep going.
Keep climbing, even on the last ascent.
I think we were both wrecked,
but Hai Guai still looked pretty lively.
What about at night?
At night,
uh...
it was miserable.
Especially on the last mountain.
After we climbed it,
we sat at the saddle in a daze.
We watched the sunrise,
and then forced ourselves to keep going.
Uh, I...
Honestly, the fact that
we made it this far together
already surprised me.
Because he was still in great shape,
and my mind was basically blank.
I was just
putting one foot in front of the other.
Don't think about what's behind you.
Harder things are still waiting ahead.
Bravo.
Thank you.
I didn't feel like I was back on earth.
Because I was heading back into the mountains later.
Only getting back to Courmayeur feels like returning to earth.
It felt so familiar,
because it's what Hai Guai and I used to do.
Not for many years, of course,
I've seen Hai Guai a few times over the last few years,
but only for fairly short runs.
But yeah,
three, four, five years ago,
we did long runs together and built that connection.
I don't quite know how to describe it,
but it's some kind of bond,
moving forward together,
taking on something big together.
It felt like we were right back there.
Even after three or four years
of not doing that.
Yeah, I mean, we talked as well,
but a lot of the time we were just moving together.
If you're really tired when you get to Donnas,
you can rest there for a long time.
I was thinking we shouldn't blow ourselves up.
And in that rhythm,
you develop a kind of synchronization.
We'd want to drink water
or eat at the same time.
It's a fascinating connection.
There can be long stretches of silence.
That kind of unspoken understanding is amazing.
Even when you don't talk,
you can still feel each other.
Like you're doing the same thing together.
You can almost sense what the other person is thinking.
Sometimes you don't want to say anything,
or something suddenly occurs to you.
I've always been curious about that,
and it just happens to be one of his strengths.
At moments like that,
we talk it through.
Time to rest.
Yeah, let's take a nap.
Finally, I can sleep.
Finally.
Oh my God.
I've been out on the course for almost thirty hours.
Can we sleep now?
I'll sleep first.
I can't hold on anymore. I'm so sleepy.
I'm going to sleep.
Yeah, I guess
I kind of lost track of time,
because I didn't have a regular sleep pattern.
But you could still feel the rhythms of the day.
And I guess the difference from normal life is
that those rhythms are defined by nature,
by the sun and the moon,
not by the rhythms
of human schedules and routines.
So for me,
in some ways,
I preferred running at night,
because it was really peaceful.
There were fewer people around,
and almost less to think about.
Because it wasn't sunny
and it wasn't hot.
You could just,
you just had to keep warm.
In some places, anyway.
But that's easy.
You just put on more layers
and keep going.
So I quite liked getting long sections done at night.
And it's just easier to focus at night.
And you also know that if you're starting to feel tired,