I might draw a slightly smaller loop.
I think that's enough.
The joy of this,
isn't really about the race.
It's about the feeling and the connection we have,
with the mountains and with nature.
That's really it. Yeah.
So I'd love to come back and feel that again,
either on my own,
or with friends, designing our own routes.
I can't say exactly,
whether there were any big things I was thinking through
while I was climbing.
There are a few things I can remember now,
nothing especially interesting,
but I'll say them anyway.
One thing I noticed,
especially during the day,
was just how many people were out in the mountains.
Older people,
young people, children, families,
hiking, running, all of it.
I just thought, wow,
the outdoor culture here is so rich. It's really impressive.
So the title of this film,
Ephemeral Mountains,
what does that mean to you?
Ephemeral?
As in "Ephemeral Mountains"?
I don't really buy that.
I don't feel anything ephemeral right now,
because they're hitting me in the face every day.
It feels very, very real,
and very hard.
Obviously, if you train really hard,
like Hai Guai does.
But as I said before, for Hai Guai,
I don't even think of it as training, exactly.
It's not like he follows some training calendar.
That's just what he does.
But, you know,
he spends a lot of time in the mountains,
and that naturally makes you faster.
But I think the core skill here,
is really understanding your body.
If you know how much water, salt, and food
your body needs,
and you can actually digest it properly,
then you can just keep going. Sleep matters too,
and that's the part I struggle with.
I never really wanted it to end.
I just wanted to keep going,
keep climbing, even on that last climb.
I felt full of energy.
Honestly, I would've been happy
if that climb had gone on for another thousand meters.
You're still smiling.
I don't know, it just feels good. And the views are amazing.
It's not just the view from the top,
it's the view every hundred meters.
Every few hundred meters, it's different.
I'd been waiting for it for
all 330 kilometers, and honestly,
when I reached the last pass,
I was sad it was the last one.
I didn't want it to be the last.
It's strange to think that was the final climb.
And it feels really special.
And I guess when I get back to normal life,
I'm going to miss that feeling of
pushing my body,
and feeling that connection with nature.
Okay, thank you.
If you want something hot, soup, tea, coffee...
Okay.
What would you like?
Perfect, thank you. Bye.
Thank you too.
It's ephemeral.
I can really feel that now.
It feels like a long time while you're inside it.
Even after the first night,
I felt like I couldn't even imagine
there were still three days left.
But the moment you stop thinking about it,
you can hardly feel it at all.
You just keep moving, and suddenly it's over.
After climbing so many mountains,
do you still like climbing?
Of course.
I'm already looking forward to the next one.
After climbing that many mountains,
I still don't feel tired of climbing.
Today was so long.
I feel like I've been climbing forever.
All that pain is just your brain talking.
It's lying to you. It wants you back in the car.
Maybe that moment is right now.
I feel like I've only done one thing.
That's all.
But as for
what it might mean,
for my life in the future,
maybe
I'll only know when it happens.
But for now,
I don't think about it much.
I don't think finishing this matters that much,
or that it's something incredible.
It's over now.
A man with thunder in his chest and a calm face
is fit to be a general.
Right now, I'm all thunder inside,
because the soles of my feet...
it hurts like hell to walk on this road.
Hai Guai and Bai Rui
have finally completed their journey of giants.
For us,
the Alps are too far away,
and 330 kilometers feels impossible.
But the moment you step outside,
nature is already right beside you.
When you really come back, this is what it looks like.
Maybe out there,
you imagined it countless times.
I've imagined it countless times.
That breakfast we had this morning,
was the happiest moment.
Maybe the happiest of the year.
Happier than Spring Festival.
How did you get up here?
Can you drive halfway up?
No, you can't.
Oh my.
We climbed all the way up here.
You're the man, Director Jia.
Call Xiaoqin.
Here she comes.
You're the best.