and to discover new paths and new routes.
That sort of thing. Yeah.
We quickly realized
that there was a real connection there.
He just took the photo from a slightly different angle.
At the end of January 2021.
Yeah, get to 50 kilometers,
change clothes there. I'll follow if I can.
I don't think I can keep up.
I think Tom is in good shape.
You're better than I am.
A lot of people say that
when you hit 50 or 100 kilometers,
that's when you feel the most tired and the most pain.
Then just walk for a while.
You rarely get the chance
to race in perfect condition.
I think
the essence of ultra running is that
you're definitely going to run into problems.
Then you deal with one problem,
And then
another problem,
and solve it.
Over 300 kilometers,
you're definitely going to face plenty of problems.
Have you looked closely at this?
What?
It's only two kilometers away.
There's a "W".
It's a waypoint.
It's a waypoint, but there's
no aid there.
Okay, um...
Uh, yes.
Aid stations may have some.
It should say refreshment.
No, not aid, refreshment. Refreshment. Okay.
This place...
It looks like The Lord of the Rings.
The Lord of the Rings.
6, 5, 4
3, 2, 1
Go.
Before starting the race,
I didn't really understand what 330 kilometers meant.
I knew it was much longer than anything I'd run before,
but it was still hard to
fully comprehend what that would feel like.
It wasn't like
I'd run during the day and sleep at night.
Some days,
I'd sleep for an hour or two in the early morning,
or a bit in the middle of the day, and then keep going.
In a way, it's like being a student
who has done a lot of practice questions.
When you face something
like the Tor des Géants,
it may be a new exam,
but it just takes everything you've learned
and rearranges it.
When you face those things again,
you may not even have
the pain you were talking about.
Sometimes you might even feel
a little happy to see the question.
Where's Bai Rui... Tom?
Bai Rui should be behind us.
His bib is 63, and mine is 64.
I didn't expect that.
Are you cold?
It's okay. I've been keeping warm.