or if the scenery in the film
speaks to you,
I think the first thing is just to try.
The path is made one step at a time.
What matters is taking action,
not obsessing over what to choose.
Whether you choose the Tor des Géants
or just go for a hike in a park,
or even leave home and walk down an unfamiliar street,
all of those things are good for you,
as long as you go out and experience them,
keep experiencing different things,
and let them accumulate over time.
I think you'll find your own path.
It's not about finishing the Tor des Géants,
or completing the PTL,
as some ultimate goal.
Don't make other people's goals your own.
Even if you achieve them,
you may not feel that happy.
You may even find
you don't know what to do next.
In the course of your own exploration,
you should have a style of your own.
Don't think that nature
has to mean mountains, seas, lakes, and so on.
In fact, nature can be the city you live in,
or the streets you walk every day.
All of that is nature too.
Don't just
only through social media,
and nature through social media.
I think the best way is to go out and experience it,
and experience more of it.
Yes.
Oh.
Back when I first started running,
whether it was a 100-kilometer race
or navigating my own way through Wugong Mountain,
when I was in the forest and hit spider webs,
my energy dropped,
and my face was covered with bugs,
Getting tangled in spider webs was so frustrating.
But that mindset
gradually carried over into
my Tor des Géants today.
When I face darkness, fatigue, or injury,
I have to keep adjusting myself,
find a way to lift my spirits and get to the next aid station.
It should be the process.
All I can say is
the memories this place left me are so beautiful.
This place is truly beautiful.
I'll try to come back every year.
I'll keep training
so that next time the experience can be even better,
not so that I can get a better result.
At the same time,
I may become calmer.
I think that's the goal I'm pursuing.
After work every day,
I run up the hill behind my workplace
and watch the sunset from afar.
I can see Qingshuijian Mountain.
I don't think,
the Alps are all that important.
That's how I feel.
Life is a,
circle.
Some people may draw a big circle
and take many paths.