In northwestern Italy,
there is a land surrounded by mountains.
Valle d'Aosta.
Mont Blanc, Matterhorn,
Gran Paradiso,
Those giants of the Alps,
silently witnessing human insignificance and courage.
Fifteen years ago, someone decided to do something crazy.
to cross the giants' territory on foot.
So,
the Tor des Géants was born.
His name is Hai Guai.
He lives in Beijing and loves climbing mountains.
The taller one is Bai Rui.
He's from Northern Ireland.
They met on Strava.
He was also living in Beijing at the time.
After that, almost every weekend,
they went into the mountains together.
Until Bai Rui returned to London.
they each got busy with their own lives,
and it became hard to meet up and climb together.
Until one day,
Hai Guai and Bai Rui decided
to take on the long-awaited Tor des Géants together.
They would cross the Aosta Valley,
covering 330 kilometers together.
And this is where
their story begins.
Yesterday, I did over 4,800 meters.
Of elevation gain?
Ah.
In forty-six kilometers.
Ah, forty-six kilometers.
Over 4,800 meters of elevation gain.
Hai Guai said he wasn't preparing for the race,
It was just a regular training day.
But for most people, a daily routine like that,
would be resume-worthy.
Look at these two pairs of shoes.
How many kilometers can one pair of shoes run?
For him, running in the forest,
to him,
is a way of returning to nature
and to himself.
Every weekend,
he heads into the mountains to recharge.
This is where trail runners in Beijing
do their everyday training.
Everyone knows this place well.
When Bai Rui and I were running in Sanfeng,
we talked about whether
we should sign up for a race together.
After he moved back to London,
we knew that chances to explore the mountains together,
would only get rarer.
A race felt like the best way to do it.
I wanted to do a multi-day race.
That way, we could spend a lot of time together.
If we just ran a 100K,
or a hundred-miler,
we probably wouldn't even have time to hang out afterward.
A multi-day race seemed much better.
My name is Tom. I'm originally from Ireland,
but I live in London now.
And London is a big city, far from the mountains.
But every weekend, I get out to the local hills.
We did a few runs together and
quickly realized that our attitudes toward
running and trail running were very similar,
that we both used it as a way to explore the mountains,
to explore the wilderness,