or whatever, you know that in a few hours,
the sun will start coming up,
and it's so beautiful that all your energy comes back.
He comes alive at night.
I think he's going to tear me apart. Let's go.
Let's go.
Oh my god.
This trail...
It's indescribable.
Hai Guai said it was indescribable.
I think he was just too tired,
so tired that even the wind felt like a burden.
But when they saw the mountains
and the clouds,
their eyes lit up again.
People who spend time outdoors know that feeling:
your body is in hell,
but your eyes are in heaven.
And time
is always contradictory.
They want it to go faster
so they can get it over with,
but they also want it to slow down,
because they don't want to fast-forward through the scenery.
You really know how to pick a spot.
The prettiest internet-famous hut.
On either side of every saddle,
the temperature
can be completely different.
So when you come out of the forest
and see the meadow or the boulder field,
your spirits lift,
and the fatigue eases a little.
Every stretch around a summit is the essence of it.
I don't know. It's really hard to comprehend
before you've done a race like this.
It's basically one huge climb,
because I slept in Donnas
and then left at around
eleven-thirty or midnight.
There's basically a 2,400-meter climb.
But one thing that surprised me was
that even with all the ups and downs,
in some ways
you actually feel stronger as the race goes on.
It sounds strange to say that because obviously
I slowed down, and by the end
my quads were kind of injured, not really injured,
but overused and swollen.
But even so, on the final climb,
I felt strong,
I felt stronger on the last hill
than I did on the first few.
I felt like I'd adapted.
The other thing I was thinking about a lot,
whenever my brain was still awake
and I wasn't too tired,
was how much I wanted to
come back to this area,
and explore other paths,
just on my own,
outside of a race format.
We crossed so many different trails,
and there are so many beautiful places,
I'd like to come back to new places,
to keep exploring.
Ten years ago,
when I saw others complete the Tor des Géants,
I was still a chubby guy weighing about 85 kilos.
I lost weight, and then I got into the sport.
If you really like it,
and if this film moves you,