I may draw a slightly smaller circle.
I think it's enough.
The joy of doing this,
is not about the race.
It's about the feeling and connections we get,
with the mountains and nature,
and so on. Yeah,
so I'd like to come back and experience that again,
and just on my own,
or just with friends, design our own routes.
I can't think like exactly,
were there any major things I was thinking through,
while I was going up.
There's a few like I can recall a few things now,
that are not very interesting,
but I'm gonna say them anyway.
I noticed during particularly,
during the day,
just how many people were out and about in the mountains.
like old people,
young people, children, families,
hiking, running, and all that.
I just thought wow,
the outdoors culture here is so rich, it's really impressive.
So the title of this film,
Ephemeral mountains，
what does that like mean to you？
ephemeral？
It's like ephemeral mountains.
I don't got that，
I don't feel very ephemeral at the moment，
because they're hitting me in the face every day.
It feels very very real，
and very hard.
Obviously, if you train really hard，
like, I mean, like Hai Guai.
As I said before like, for Hai Guai,
I don't think it's like training per se.
it's not like he has a calendar of like a training plan.
just what he does.
but you know
He does a lot of mountains,
and with that you will be faster.
But I think the core skill in this,
really is understanding your body.
Like if you can understand how much water, salt, and food,
your body needs,
and if you can digest it properly and so on,
you can just keep going and sleep as well,
which is the bit I'm struggling with.
I never felt like I wanted it to end or whatever.
I just wanted to keep going,
keep climbing even on the last climb there.
I felt a lot of energy.
I would have been happy,
if that climb had gone on for another thousand meters.
You're still smiling.
I don't know, it feels good, and the views from every point.
It's not just the view from the top,
it's the view from every hundred meters.
Every couple hundred meters is different.
I've been waiting for it for
three hundred and thirty kilometers, and honestly,
when I got to the last pass,
you konw I was sad that it was the last pass.
I didn't want it to be the last one.
Weird to think that it's the last climb.
And it feels really special.
And I guess when I get back to normal life,
I'm gonna feel like I miss that feeling of,
pushing my body，
and feeling the connection with nature.
OK, thank you.
If you want something too hot, soup, tea, coffee.
OK.
where do you want？
Perfect, thank you, bye.
thank you too.
It's ephemeral.
I really feel like ephemeral.
It feels like a long time when you're in it.
Even after the first night,
I felt like I couldn't even imagine，
there are still three days left.
When you briefly let go of these thoughts,
you can't feel it.
As you walk, you don't realize that it's all over.
After climbing so many mountains,
Do you still like climbing mountains？
Of course.
I'm already looking forward to the next time.
Climbing so many mountains.
I feel like I didn't get tired to the top.
Today is so long.
I feel like I've been climbing for a long time.
Your pain is all told by your brain,
It's a lie, and it want you to fly a drone in the car.
It might be here now.
I just accomplished one thing.
that's all.
But as for,
in the future,
what impact it will have on your future life,
I said maybe.
I may only know when it happens.
As for now,
I don't think so much.
I don't think it's that important to finish this,
or how amazing it is.
It's over.
A man with thunder in his chest but calm face,
can be made a general.
I'm like with thunder now.
because my soles,
and it hurts a lot to walk on this road.
Hai Gui and Bai Rui,
have finally completed their giant journey.
For us,
Alps is too far,
three hundred and thirty kilometers is too hard.
But when you open the door and go out,
your nature is right beside you.
When you really come back, this is the scene.
Maybe on the way,
you've thought about it countless times.
I've thought about it countless times.
The breakfast we had in the morning,
It was the happiest time.
Maybe the happiest time of the year.
It's happier than the Spring Festival.
How did you get up here？
Can you drive to the halfway up？
No, I can't.
Oh my.
We climb here.
You are the man Director Jia.
Call Xiaoqin.
Here comes.
You are the best.