Is it okay？ Are you cold？
I am okay.
Water.
To the challenges over those days.
Another surprising thing is just how little sleep one needs.
I mean I got far more sleep than Hai Guai.
But it was still only like eight hours or something.
Kyle, you've worked hard.
Bai Rui has long Stride Length.
I could run while he could walk.
Really.
I mostly felt fine.
There was one time,
where I went over some kind of limit of,
not having enough sleep.
But after that I managed to deal with it fairly well.
And I realized that,
Actually like sometimes you only need an hour of sleep,
and then you can keep going.
Bai Rui and I were both exhausted.
And that mountain,
It felt like we were zigzagging up the mountain.
On zigzag uphill,
But it is.
It was very gentle, but then we got angry,
And started to climb straight up.
I felt like i was blew up.
Two three-kilometer mountains.
The first one was difficult.
The second one was even harder.
The only times I felt like I really wanted this to finish,
or like I really wanted to get to the next aid station,
or whatever was on some of the really long downhill.
There were some really long downhill sections,
That were just,
painful, and I mean that's why,
that's why,
My quads froze up at the end because of those downhills.
But other than that, I mean,
going up the mountains, I don't know.
I never felt like I wanted it to end,
or whatever I kind of,
I just wanted to keep going.
Keep climbing even on the last climb there.
I was saying I think we were both wrecked,
but Hai Guai actually looked pretty lively.
How about the evening?
At night,
Uh.
It was miserable.
Especially on the last mountain,
After climbing the last mountain,
we sat at the saddle in a daze,
We watched the sunrise,
and then we mustered up the courage to continue.
Uh, I
Actually, we can together run to here,
I already felt quite surprised.
Because he was in a very good state,
And I didn't seem to be in any mood.
Just mechanically,
put one foot in front of the other,
and keep going.
Don't think about what's behind.
Because there are more difficult things waiting for you.
Bravo.
Thank you.
I didn't feel like I was back on earth.
Because I will go back to the mountain later.
Only returning to Courmayeur is called returning to earth.
It felt so familiar,
Because it's what me and Hai guai have done before.
Although not for many many years,
I've seen Hai guai a few times over the last few years,
but for fairly short runs.
But yeah.
Three or four or five years ago,
we did long runs together and formed that connection.
Which I don't know what the word to describe it,
but there's some kind of connection of like,
Moving forward together, doing something together,
doing a big challenge and yeah,
It felt like we were right back in that.
After three or four years of,
not doing that.
Yeah, I mean we talked about stuff as well,
but it was a lot of time just yeah just moving together.
If you are so tired when arrive Donnas,
you can rest for long time there, I was thinking,
we should not so blow up.
In tune as well,
you kind of develop a kind of synchronization.
Where we both need to drink water,
at the same time or eat at the same time, and yeah.
This is just an interesting connection.
There will be long periods of silence.
I think this kind of tacit understanding is amazing.
Even when you don't talk,
you can also feel each other.
We are doing something.
You can feel what the other person seems to be saying.
Sometimes you may not want to say anything,
or suddenly think of something.
I've always been curious about it,
but it happens to be his strength.
At this time,
and discuss it.
Time to rest.
Yes, let's take a nap.
Finally, I can sleep.
Finally finally.
Oh my god.
I've been on the road for almost thirty hours.
Can we sleep now？
I'll go to sleep first.
I can't hold on anymore, I'm so sleepy.
I'll go to sleep.
Yeah, I guess like
I kind of lost track of time in a way,
because I didn't have a regular sleeping pattern.
But you can still feel the kind of rhythms of the day.
And I guess like the difference with normal life is,
It's the rhythms of the day as defined by nature.
The sun and the moon,
not the rhythms of the day defined by,
human schedules and so on.
So for me,
in some ways,
I preferred running at night
because it was really peaceful.
there were less people around,
and less almost like less to think about.
Because it wasn't sunny,
it wasn't hot,
like you could just,
you just need to keep warm.
but in some places you need to keep warm.
But that's easy,
you just put on more layers,
and then keep going.
So I quite like getting long sections done at night.
And it's just easy to focus at night.
And then you also know that if you're starting to feel tired,