In the northwest of Italy,
There is a land surrounded by mountains.
Valle d'Aosta
Mont Blanc, Matterhorn,
Gran Paradiso,
Those giants of the Alps,
silently watching human's insignificance and courage.
Fifteen years ago, someone wanted to do a crazy thing.
to cross the giants' territory on foot.
So,
the Tor des Géants was born.
His name is Hai Guai.
He lives in Beijing and loves climbing mountains.
The tall one is Bai Rui.
He's from Northern Ireland.
They met on Strava.
He was also in Beijing at that time.
Later, almost every weekend,
They went into the mountains together.
Until Bai Rui returned to London.
They were busy with their own affairs
and it was hard to meet and climb together.
Until one day,
Hai Gui and Bai Rui made an appointment
to explore the long-awaited “Tor des Géants” together.
They will explore the Aosta Valley,
and cross three hundred and thirty kilometers together.
And this story belongs to them,
begins.
Yesterday, I ran over four thousand eight hundred.
Elevation gain？
Ah.
Forty-six kilometers.
Ah, forty-six kilometers.
Over four thousand eight hundred elevation gain.
Hai Gui said he wasn't preparing for the race,
It's just daily training.
But for others, this daily routine,
It would be written in their resumes.
Look at these two pairs of shoes.
How many kilometers can a pair of shoes run？
Running in the forest,
to him,
is returning to nature.
and back to himself.
Every weekend,
he goes into the mountains to charge his life.
The daily training of trail runners in Beijing,
is all around here.
which is very familiar to everyone.
When Bai Rui and I were running in Sanfeng,
We discussed whether,
we should sign up for a race together.
After he returned to London,
We agreed to explore some mountains together,
this opportunity may become less and less.
Races becomes a better form.
I would like to participate in a multi-day race.
We can spend a lot of time together.
If we really run a hundred kilometers,
or a hundred-mile race,
we wouldn't even have time to meet after the race.
But multi-day races might be much better.
My name is Tom, I'm from Ireland originally,
But I live in London now.
And London is a big city far away from mountains.
But every weekend I get out either to the local hills.
We did a few runs together and quite
Quickly realized that our attitudes towards
running and trail running is very similar.
Which is like using it as a way to explore the mountains,
explore wilderness.
And to discover new paths and new routes to travel
And so on. Yeah.
We quickly realized that
We had a kind of connection there, it was around there
He took the photo from a slightly different angle.
In twenty twenty one, end of January twenty twenty one.
Yeah, get through to fifty kilometers,
changed clothes there. I will follow you if i could.
I think I can't follow.
I think Tom are in good condition.
You're better than me.
Many people said that
When you reach fifty or one hundred kilometers,
you may feel the most tired and painful.
Then take a walk.
You rarely have the opportunity to
In a perfect state to compete.
I think, and
the essence of Ultra is that
You will definitely encounter problems.
Then you encounter problems,
And then
Encounter problems,
Solve problems.
Within three hundred kilometers,
You will definitely encounter many problems.
Have you look carefully at this,
What
It's only two kilometers away.
There is a "W".
It's a waypoint.
It's a way point, but there is no.
No supplies.
OK, um.
Uh, yes.
Aid A for aid aid may have some.
It should be Refreshment.
It's not, it's refreshment. Refreshment. Okay.
This is.
It's looks like The Lord of the Rings.
The Lord of the Rings.
6、5、4
3、2、1
Go.
Before starting the race,
I didn't really understand how long three thirty was.
I mean i know it was much longer than I'd run before.
But it's still hard to
comperhanding exactly what that feels like.
It's not like,
I wasn't running on the day and sleeping at night.
Like some days,
I sleep for an hour or two in the early morning,
or sleep bit  in the middle of the day, and then keep going.
In fact, you are like a student,
and you do a lot of exam questions.
When you face something like,
such as the Tor des Géants.
it may be a new exam,
It will take the knowledge points you have learned,
and then reassemble them.
When you face these again,
You may not have that,
the painful feeling you mentioned.
Sometimes you might even feel,
a little happy about hitting the question.
Where's Bai Rui(Tom)？
Bai Rui should be behind.
He's Bib is sixty-three, and I'm sixty-four.
I didn't expect
Are you cold？
It's okay, I've been keeping warm.