or whatever, you know that in a few hours time,
the sun will start to coming up,
and it's just beautiful and all your energy comes back.
He'll recover at night.
I think he's going to pull me apart. Let's go.
Let's go.
Oh my god.
This track.
It's indescribable.
Hai Guai said it was indescribable.
I think he was too tired,
so tired that even the wind became a burden.
But when they saw the mountains,
and clouds,
their eyes suddenly lit up again.
It's like outdoor people know that feeling,
body in hell,
and eyes in heaven.
And time,
is always contradictory.
They hope it goes faster,
so that they can end it all quickly,
but also hope it slows down,
because they don't want to fast-forward the scenery.
You really know how to choose the place.
The most beautiful internet-famous cottage.
The front and back of each saddle,
and temperature.
which are all different.
So when you come out of the forest,
you see the meadow or the stone sea,
your spirits will be lifted,
and the fatigue will be slightly relieved.
Every time around the top of the mountain is the essence.
I don't know it's really hard to comperhand,
before having done a race like this.
it's basically just one big climb,
because I slept in the Donnas.
and then leave until about half past,
eleven or midnight.
There's basically a two thousand four hundred meter climb.
But the things that surprised me I guess was,
where you go through ups and downs,
but in some ways,
you kind of feel stronger through the run.
Sounds weird to say that because obviously,
I slowed down and by the end like,
I was kind of injured on my quads, not really injured,
but it was overused and swollen.
But still at the end, when I was going uphill, at least,
I felt strong,
I felt stronger going up the final hill,
than the first few hills.
I felt like I had adapted.
the other thing I was thinking about quite a lot, at least,
while my brain was fairly awake,
and not too tired.
I was thinking a lot about how I wanted to,
come back to this area,
and explore other paths.
just like on my own,
not in a race format.
We crossed over so many different paths,
and there are so many beautiful places,
I'd like to go back to new places,
I'd like to explore.
Ten years ago,
when I saw others complete the Tor des Géants,
I was also a fat guy weighing one hundred seventy catties.
I also lost weight and then got into this sport.
If you really like it,
and think this film is good,
or the scenery shown in the film,
which touches you,
I think you can try to do it first.
The road is made step by step.
The important thing is to take action,
rather than choosing what to do.
Whether you choose Tor des Géants
or take a park hike,
or even just leave home and walk to a strange street,
these are both good things to you,
as long as you go out and experience,
and experience different things,
and accumulate them gradually.
I think you may have your own path.
It's not about completing the Tor des Géants,
or complete the PTL,
as your ultimate goal.
Don't take others' goals as your own.
Even if you achieve it,
you may not feel very happy.
You may even feel,
you may not know what to do next.
In the process of your own exploration,
have your own style.
Don't think that nature is,
may be defined as mountains, seas, lakes, and so on.
In fact, nature is the city where you live,
or maybe the streets where you live.
These are all nature.
Don't say that you only look at the world,
only through social media,
and see nature.
I think the best way is to go out and experience it,
and experience more.
Yes.
Oh.
When I was running in early times,
run one hundred kilometers,
or navigate myself to Wugong Mountain,
when I was in the forest and encountered spider webs,
my physical strength decreased,
and my face was covered with bugs,
I was very frustrated when I was covered in spider webs.
This is the mentality,
and gradually it may transfer to,
my current Tor des Géants.
when facing darkness, fatigue or injury,
I have to adjust myself.
how to cheer up and move on to the next supply station.
It should be the process.
I can only say,
the memories left by this place are so beautiful.
This place is really beautiful.
I will try to come back every year.
I will still train myself,
to make my next experence better.
Not that I'll get better results.
In the same time,
I might become more calm.
I think this is the goal I pursue.
When I get off work every day,
I run to the back mountain near my workplace,
and watch the sunset from a distance.
I can see the Qingshuijian Mountain,
I don't think,
the Alps are particularly important.
I feel like this.
Life is a,
circle.
Some people may draw a big circle,
and take many paths.