or whatever, you know that in a few hours time,
the sun will start to coming up,
and it's just beautiful and all your energy comes back.
He'll recover at night.
I think he's going to pull me apart. Let's go.
Let's go.
Oh my god.
This track.
It's indescribable.
Hai Guai said it was indescribable.
I think he was too tired,
so tired that even the wind became a burden.
But when they saw the mountains,
and clouds,
their eyes suddenly lit up again.
It's like outdoor people know that feeling,
body in hell,
and eyes in heaven.
And time,
is always contradictory.
They hope it goes faster,
so that they can end it all quickly,
but also hope it slows down,
because they don't want to fast-forward the scenery.
You really know how to choose the place.
The most beautiful internet-famous cottage.
The front and back of each saddle,
and temperature.
which are all different.
So when you come out of the forest,
you see the meadow or the stone sea,
your spirits will be lifted,
and the fatigue will be slightly relieved.
Every time around the top of the mountain is the essence.
I don't know it's really hard to comperhand,
before having done a race like this.
it's basically just one big climb,
because I slept in the Donnas.
and then leave until about half past,
eleven or midnight.
There's basically a two thousand four hundred meter climb.
But the things that surprised me I guess was,
where you go through ups and downs,
but in some ways,
you kind of feel stronger through the run.
Sounds weird to say that because obviously,
I slowed down and by the end like,
I was kind of injured on my quads, not really injured,
but it was overused and swollen.
But still at the end, when I was going uphill, at least,
I felt strong,
I felt stronger going up the final hill,
than the first few hills.
I felt like I had adapted.
the other thing I was thinking about quite a lot, at least,
while my brain was fairly awake,
and not too tired.
I was thinking a lot about how I wanted to,
come back to this area,
and explore other paths.
just like on my own,
not in a race format.
We crossed over so many different paths,
and there are so many beautiful places,
I'd like to go back to new places,
I'd like to explore.
Ten years ago,
when I saw others complete the Tor des Géants,
I was also a fat guy weighing one hundred seventy catties.
I also lost weight and then got into this sport.
If you really like it,
and think this film is good,