In the northwest of Italy,
There is a land surrounded by mountains.
Valle d'Aosta
Mont Blanc, Matterhorn,
Gran Paradiso,
Those giants of the Alps,
silently watching human's insignificance and courage.
Fifteen years ago, someone wanted to do a crazy thing.
to cross the giants' territory on foot.
So,
the Tor des Géants was born.
His name is Hai Guai.
He lives in Beijing and loves climbing mountains.
The tall one is Bai Rui.
He's from Northern Ireland.
They met on Strava.
He was also in Beijing at that time.
Later, almost every weekend,
They went into the mountains together.
Until Bai Rui returned to London.
They were busy with their own affairs
and it was hard to meet and climb together.
Until one day,
Hai Gui and Bai Rui made an appointment
to explore the long-awaited “Tor des Géants” together.
They will explore the Aosta Valley,
and cross three hundred and thirty kilometers together.
And this story belongs to them,
begins.
Yesterday, I ran over four thousand eight hundred.
Elevation gain？
Ah.
Forty-six kilometers.
Ah, forty-six kilometers.
Over four thousand eight hundred elevation gain.
Hai Gui said he wasn't preparing for the race,
It's just daily training.
But for others, this daily routine,
It would be written in their resumes.
Look at these two pairs of shoes.
How many kilometers can a pair of shoes run？
Running in the forest,
to him,
is returning to nature.
and back to himself.
Every weekend,
he goes into the mountains to charge his life.
The daily training of trail runners in Beijing,
is all around here.
which is very familiar to everyone.
When Bai Rui and I were running in Sanfeng,
We discussed whether,
we should sign up for a race together.
After he returned to London,
We agreed to explore some mountains together,
this opportunity may become less and less.
Races becomes a better form.
I would like to participate in a multi-day race.
We can spend a lot of time together.
If we really run a hundred kilometers,
or a hundred-mile race,
we wouldn't even have time to meet after the race.
But multi-day races might be much better.
My name is Tom, I'm from Ireland originally,
But I live in London now.
And London is a big city far away from mountains.
But every weekend I get out either to the local hills.
We did a few runs together and quite
Quickly realized that our attitudes towards
running and trail running is very similar.
Which is like using it as a way to explore the mountains,
explore wilderness.