or the scenery shown in the film,
which touches you,
I think you can try to do it first.
The road is made step by step.
The important thing is to take action,
rather than choosing what to do.
Whether you choose Tor des Géants
or take a park hike,
or even just leave home and walk to a strange street,
these are both good things to you,
as long as you go out and experience,
and experience different things,
and accumulate them gradually.
I think you may have your own path.
It's not about completing the Tor des Géants,
or complete the PTL,
as your ultimate goal.
Don't take others' goals as your own.
Even if you achieve it,
you may not feel very happy.
You may even feel,
you may not know what to do next.
In the process of your own exploration,
have your own style.
Don't think that nature is,
may be defined as mountains, seas, lakes, and so on.
In fact, nature is the city where you live,
or maybe the streets where you live.
These are all nature.
Don't say that you only look at the world,
only through social media,
and see nature.
I think the best way is to go out and experience it,
and experience more.
Yes.
Oh.
When I was running in early times,
run one hundred kilometers,
or navigate myself to Wugong Mountain,
when I was in the forest and encountered spider webs,
my physical strength decreased,
and my face was covered with bugs,
I was very frustrated when I was covered in spider webs.
This is the mentality,
and gradually it may transfer to,
my current Tor des Géants.
when facing darkness, fatigue or injury,
I have to adjust myself.
how to cheer up and move on to the next supply station.
It should be the process.
I can only say,
the memories left by this place are so beautiful.
This place is really beautiful.
I will try to come back every year.
I will still train myself,
to make my next experence better.
Not that I'll get better results.
In the same time,
I might become more calm.
I think this is the goal I pursue.
When I get off work every day,
I run to the back mountain near my workplace,
and watch the sunset from a distance.
I can see the Qingshuijian Mountain,
I don't think,
the Alps are particularly important.
I feel like this.
Life is a,
circle.
Some people may draw a big circle,
and take many paths.