And to discover new paths and new routes to travel
And so on. Yeah.
We quickly realized that
We had a kind of connection there, it was around there
He took the photo from a slightly different angle.
In twenty twenty one, end of January twenty twenty one.
Yeah, get through to fifty kilometers,
changed clothes there. I will follow you if i could.
I think I can't follow.
I think Tom are in good condition.
You're better than me.
Many people said that
When you reach fifty or one hundred kilometers,
you may feel the most tired and painful.
Then take a walk.
You rarely have the opportunity to
In a perfect state to compete.
I think, and
the essence of Ultra is that
You will definitely encounter problems.
Then you encounter problems,
And then
Encounter problems,
Solve problems.
Within three hundred kilometers,
You will definitely encounter many problems.
Have you look carefully at this,
What
It's only two kilometers away.
There is a "W".
It's a waypoint.
It's a way point, but there is no.
No supplies.
OK, um.
Uh, yes.
Aid A for aid aid may have some.
It should be Refreshment.
It's not, it's refreshment. Refreshment. Okay.
This is.
It's looks like The Lord of the Rings.
The Lord of the Rings.
6、5、4
3、2、1
Go.
Before starting the race,
I didn't really understand how long three thirty was.
I mean i know it was much longer than I'd run before.
But it's still hard to
comperhanding exactly what that feels like.
It's not like,
I wasn't running on the day and sleeping at night.
Like some days,
I sleep for an hour or two in the early morning,
or sleep bit  in the middle of the day, and then keep going.
In fact, you are like a student,
and you do a lot of exam questions.
When you face something like,
such as the Tor des Géants.
it may be a new exam,
It will take the knowledge points you have learned,
and then reassemble them.
When you face these again,
You may not have that,
the painful feeling you mentioned.
Sometimes you might even feel,
a little happy about hitting the question.
Where's Bai Rui(Tom)？
Bai Rui should be behind.
He's Bib is sixty-three, and I'm sixty-four.
I didn't expect
Are you cold？
It's okay, I've been keeping warm.