In the northwest of Italy,
there is a land ringed by mountains.
Valle d'Aosta.
Mont Blanc, Matterhorn,
Gran Paradiso,
those giants of the Alps,
silently witnessing human insignificance and courage.
Fifteen years ago, someone wanted to do something crazy:
cross the land of giants on foot.
So,
the Tor des Geants was born.
His name is Hai Guai.
He lives in Beijing and loves the mountains.
The tall one is Bai Rui.
He's from Northern Ireland.
They met on Strava.
He was living in Beijing then too.
Later, almost every weekend,
they headed into the mountains together.
Until Bai Rui moved back to London.
They each got busy with life,
and it became hard to meet and run together.
Until one day,
Hai Guai and Bai Rui decided
to take on the long-awaited Tor des Geants together.
They would cross the Aosta Valley
and cover 330 kilometers together.
And this is where
their story begins.
Yesterday, I did over 4,800 meters.
Of elevation gain?
Yeah.
Forty-six kilometers.
Ah, forty-six kilometers.
Over 4,800 meters of climbing.
Hai Guai said he wasn't preparing for a race.
It was just a regular training day.
But for most people,
that alone would be resume-worthy.
Look at these two pairs of shoes.
How many kilometers can one pair last?
Running through the forest,
for him,
is a return to nature
and a return to himself.
Every weekend,
he heads into the mountains to recharge.
For trail runners in Beijing,
this is where they do
their everyday training.
When Bai Rui and I were running in Sanfeng,
we talked about whether
we should sign up for a race together.
After he moved back to London,
we both felt that chances
to explore the mountains together
would only get rarer.
So I wanted to do a multi-day race.
That way, we could spend a lot of time together.
If we just ran 100 kilometers,
or a 100-mile race,
we probably would not even have time
to really be together afterward.
My name is Tom. I'm originally from Ireland,
but I live in London now.
And London is a big city, far from the mountains.
But every weekend I try to get out to the nearby hills.
We did a few runs together and quite
quickly realized that our attitudes toward
running and trail running were very similar.
We both saw it as a way to explore the mountains,
and explore the wilderness.
and discover new paths and new routes.
That kind of thing, yeah.
We quickly realized
that we had that kind of connection. It started around then.
He took the photo from a slightly different angle.
At the end of January 2021.
Yeah, once we got to fifty kilometers,
we changed clothes there. I'd follow you if I could.
I don't think I can keep up.
I think Tom is in good shape.
You're better than me.
A lot of people say that
When you reach fifty or one hundred kilometers,
you may feel the most tired and painful.
Then you just have to walk.
You rarely get the chance to race
in a perfect state.
I think
the essence of an ultra is that
you're bound to run into problems.
You deal with one problem,
and then
another one comes,
and you solve it.
Over three hundred kilometers,
you're bound to face plenty of problems.
Have you looked closely at this?
What?
It's only two kilometers away.
There is a "W".
It's a waypoint.
It's a waypoint, but there's nothing there.
No supplies.
OK, um.
Uh, yes.
Aid A might have some.
It should mean refreshment.
Not aid. Refreshment. Right.
This place
looks like The Lord of the Rings.
The Lord of the Rings.
6, 5, 4
3, 2, 1
Go.
Before starting the race,
I didn't really understand what three thirty meant.
I mean, I knew it was much farther than I'd ever run before.
But it's still hard to
fully comprehend what that would feel like.
It's not like,
you run in the day and sleep at night.
Some days,
I'd sleep for an hour or two in the early morning,
or catch a bit of sleep in the middle of the day, then keep going.
Actually, it's like being a student,
doing lots of practice questions.
When you face something
like the Tor des Géants,
it's a new kind of exam.
It takes everything you've learned
and rearranges it.
When you face those problems again,
you may not feel
the pain you used to talk about.
Sometimes you might even feel
a little excited to see the question.
Where's Bai Rui?
Bai Rui should be behind us.
His bib is sixty-three, and I'm sixty-four.
I didn't expect that.
Are you cold?
It's okay. I've been keeping warm.
Are you okay? Are you cold?
I'm okay.
Water.
To the challenges ahead.
Another surprising thing is how little sleep you actually need.
I mean, I got far more sleep than Hai Guai.
But it was still only about eight hours in total.
Kyle, you've worked hard.
Bai Rui has a long stride.
I have to run while he's just walking.
Really.
I mostly felt fine.
There was one point
when I hit some kind of limit
from not getting enough sleep.
But after that, I managed it pretty well.
And I realized
that sometimes an hour of sleep is enough,
and then you can keep going.
Bai Rui and I were both exhausted.
And on that mountain,
it felt like we were just zigzagging forever.
The switchbacks
were gentle,
but then we got frustrated
and started climbing straight up.
I felt completely blown up.
Two three-kilometer climbs.
The first one was hard.
The second one was even harder.
The only times I really wanted it to end
or really wanted to reach the next aid station
were on some of the really long downhills.
There were some downhill sections
that were just
painful, and I mean,
that's why,
my quads seized up at the end.
But other than that,
going up the mountains,
I never really felt like I wanted it to end.
If anything,
I just wanted to keep going.
Keep climbing, even on the last ascent.
I think we were both wrecked,
but Hai Guai still looked pretty lively.
What about at night?
At night,
uh...
it was miserable.
Especially on the last mountain.
After we climbed it,
we sat at the saddle in a daze.
We watched the sunrise,
and then forced ourselves to keep going.
Uh, I...
Honestly, the fact that
we made it this far together
already surprised me.
Because he was still in great shape,
and my mind was basically blank.
I was just
putting one foot in front of the other.
Don't think about what's behind you.
Harder things are still waiting ahead.
Bravo.
Thank you.
I didn't feel like I was back on earth.
Because I was heading back into the mountains later.
Only getting back to Courmayeur feels like returning to earth.
It felt so familiar,
because it's what Hai Guai and I used to do.
Not for many years, of course,
I've seen Hai Guai a few times over the last few years,
but only for fairly short runs.
But yeah,
three, four, five years ago,
we did long runs together and built that connection.
I don't quite know how to describe it,
but it's some kind of bond,
moving forward together,
taking on something big together.
It felt like we were right back there.
Even after three or four years
of not doing that.
Yeah, I mean, we talked as well,
but a lot of the time we were just moving together.
If you're really tired when you get to Donnas,
you can rest there for a long time.
I was thinking we shouldn't blow ourselves up.
And in that rhythm,
you develop a kind of synchronization.
We'd want to drink water
or eat at the same time.
It's a fascinating connection.
There can be long stretches of silence.
That kind of unspoken understanding is amazing.
Even when you don't talk,
you can still feel each other.
Like you're doing the same thing together.
You can almost sense what the other person is thinking.
Sometimes you don't want to say anything,
or something suddenly occurs to you.
I've always been curious about that,
and it just happens to be one of his strengths.
At moments like that,
we talk it through.
Time to rest.
Yeah, let's take a nap.
Finally, I can sleep.
Finally.
Oh my God.
I've been out on the course for almost thirty hours.
Can we sleep now?
I'll sleep first.
I can't hold on anymore. I'm so sleepy.
I'm going to sleep.
Yeah, I guess
I kind of lost track of time,
because I didn't have a regular sleep pattern.
But you could still feel the rhythms of the day.
And I guess the difference from normal life is
that those rhythms are defined by nature,
by the sun and the moon,
not by the rhythms
of human schedules and routines.
So for me,
in some ways,
I preferred running at night,
because it was really peaceful.
There were fewer people around,
and almost less to think about.
Because it wasn't sunny
and it wasn't hot.
You could just,
you just had to keep warm.
In some places, anyway.
But that's easy.
You just put on more layers
and keep going.
So I quite liked getting long sections done at night.
And it's just easier to focus at night.
And you also know that if you're starting to feel tired,
or whatever. You know that in a few hours,
the sun will start coming up,
and it's so beautiful that all your energy comes back.
He recovers at night.
I think he's going to drop me. Let's go.
Let's go.
Oh my God.
This trail.
It's indescribable.
Hai Guai said it was indescribable.
I think he was just too tired,
so tired that even the wind felt like a burden.
But when they looked up at the mountains
and the clouds,
their eyes lit up again.
If you've spent time outdoors, you know that feeling:
your body in hell,
your eyes in heaven.
And time
is always full of contradictions.
They want it to go faster,
so they can get it over with,
but they also want it to slow down,
because they don't want to rush past the scenery.
You really know how to pick a spot.
The most photogenic cabin of all.
The front and back of every ridge,
and even the temperature,
are all different.
So when you come out of the forest
and see the meadow or the scree,
your spirits lift,
and the fatigue eases a little.
Every stretch near the summit is the best part.
I don't know. It's really hard to comprehend,
before you've done a race like this,
that it's basically one huge climb,
because I slept in Donnas
and didn't leave until about
eleven-thirty or midnight.
There's basically a 2,400-meter climb.
But one thing that surprised me was,
even though you go through so many ups and downs,
in some ways,
you actually start to feel stronger as the race goes on.
It sounds strange to say that, because obviously,
I slowed down, and by the end,
my quads were pretty wrecked. Not injured exactly,
but overused and swollen.
But even at the end, at least on the climbs,
I still felt strong.
I felt stronger going up the final hill
than I did on the first few.
I felt like I had adapted.
The other thing I kept thinking about,
at least while my brain was still fairly awake
and I wasn't too tired,
was how much I wanted to
come back to this area
and explore other paths,
just on my own,
not as part of a race.
We crossed so many different trails,
and there were so many beautiful places.
I'd love to come back
and explore them properly.
Ten years ago,
when I saw other people finish the Tor des Géants,
I was also overweight, about 85 kilos.
I lost weight and then got into this sport.
If you really like it,
and think this film is good,
or the scenery shown in the film,
moves you,
then I think you should try it for yourself.
Every road is built one step at a time.
The important thing is to take action,
not overthinking what to choose.
Whether you choose Tor des Géants
or take a park hike,
or even just step outside
and walk down an unfamiliar street,
all of that is worthwhile
as long as you go out and experience life,
and slowly build it up.
I think everyone has their own path.
It doesn't have to be about finishing the Tor des Géants
or complete the PTL,
as your ultimate goal.
Don't take others' goals as your own.
Even if you achieve it,
you may not feel very happy.
You may even feel,
you may not know what to do next.
In the course of your own exploration,
you have to find your own style.
Don't think nature
only means mountains, seas, or lakes.
Nature can also be the city you live in
or the streets around you.
That's nature too.
Don't just look at the world
through social media
and call that seeing nature.
I think the best way is to go out and experience it,
and keep experiencing more.
Yes.
Oh.
Back when I first started running,
whether it was a hundred-kilometer race,
or finding my own way through Wugong Mountain,
when I was in the forest and encountered spider webs,
my energy would drop,
my face would be covered with bugs,
and I'd get really frustrated.
But that's all part of the mindset.
Little by little, it carries over
to my Tor des Géants now.
When I'm dealing with darkness, fatigue, or injury,
I have to adjust myself.
I figure out how to lift my spirits and make it to the next aid station.
That's just part of the process.
All I can say is,
the memories this place leaves you with are beautiful.
This place is really beautiful.
I'll try to come back every year.
And I'll keep training,
so the next experience can be even better.
Not that I'll get better results.
At the same time,
I might become calmer.
I think that's the goal I'm after.
When I get off work every day,
I run to the back mountain near my workplace,
and watch the sunset from a distance.
I can see the Qingshuijian Mountain,
so I don't think
the Alps are uniquely important.
That's how I feel.
Life is a,
circle.
Some people may draw a big circle,
and take many paths.
I might draw a slightly smaller loop.
I think that's enough.
The joy of this,
isn't really about the race.
It's about the feeling and the connection we have,
with the mountains and with nature.
That's really it. Yeah.
So I'd love to come back and feel that again,
either on my own,
or with friends, designing our own routes.
I can't say exactly,
whether there were any big things I was thinking through
while I was climbing.
There are a few things I can remember now,
nothing especially interesting,
but I'll say them anyway.
One thing I noticed,
especially during the day,
was just how many people were out in the mountains.
Older people,
young people, children, families,
hiking, running, all of it.
I just thought, wow,
the outdoor culture here is so rich. It's really impressive.
So the title of this film,
Ephemeral Mountains,
what does that mean to you?
Ephemeral?
As in "Ephemeral Mountains"?
I don't really buy that.
I don't feel anything ephemeral right now,
because they're hitting me in the face every day.
It feels very, very real,
and very hard.
Obviously, if you train really hard,
like Hai Guai does.
But as I said before, for Hai Guai,
I don't even think of it as training, exactly.
It's not like he follows some training calendar.
That's just what he does.
But, you know,
he spends a lot of time in the mountains,
and that naturally makes you faster.
But I think the core skill here,
is really understanding your body.
If you know how much water, salt, and food
your body needs,
and you can actually digest it properly,
then you can just keep going. Sleep matters too,
and that's the part I struggle with.
I never really wanted it to end.
I just wanted to keep going,
keep climbing, even on that last climb.
I felt full of energy.
Honestly, I would've been happy
if that climb had gone on for another thousand meters.
You're still smiling.
I don't know, it just feels good. And the views are amazing.
It's not just the view from the top,
it's the view every hundred meters.
Every few hundred meters, it's different.
I'd been waiting for it for
all 330 kilometers, and honestly,
when I reached the last pass,
I was sad it was the last one.
I didn't want it to be the last.
It's strange to think that was the final climb.
And it feels really special.
And I guess when I get back to normal life,
I'm going to miss that feeling of
pushing my body,
and feeling that connection with nature.
Okay, thank you.
If you want something hot, soup, tea, coffee...
Okay.
What would you like?
Perfect, thank you. Bye.
Thank you too.
It's ephemeral.
I can really feel that now.
It feels like a long time while you're inside it.
Even after the first night,
I felt like I couldn't even imagine
there were still three days left.
But the moment you stop thinking about it,
you can hardly feel it at all.
You just keep moving, and suddenly it's over.
After climbing so many mountains,
do you still like climbing?
Of course.
I'm already looking forward to the next one.
After climbing that many mountains,
I still don't feel tired of climbing.
Today was so long.
I feel like I've been climbing forever.
All that pain is just your brain talking.
It's lying to you. It wants you back in the car.
Maybe that moment is right now.
I feel like I've only done one thing.
That's all.
But as for
what it might mean,
for my life in the future,
maybe
I'll only know when it happens.
But for now,
I don't think about it much.
I don't think finishing this matters that much,
or that it's something incredible.
It's over now.
A man with thunder in his chest and a calm face
is fit to be a general.
Right now, I'm all thunder inside,
because the soles of my feet...
it hurts like hell to walk on this road.
Hai Guai and Bai Rui
have finally completed their journey of giants.
For us,
the Alps are too far away,
and 330 kilometers feels impossible.
But the moment you step outside,
nature is already right beside you.
When you really come back, this is what it looks like.
Maybe out there,
you imagined it countless times.
I've imagined it countless times.
That breakfast we had this morning,
was the happiest moment.
Maybe the happiest of the year.
Happier than Spring Festival.
How did you get up here?
Can you drive halfway up?
No, you can't.
Oh my.
We climbed all the way up here.
You're the man, Director Jia.
Call Xiaoqin.
Here she comes.
You're the best.